Mss.530.1.Ar2.5
American Philosophical Society
- VIII. Working Papers - Correspondence (Physicists), 2.0 Linear feet (Box 20-21)
  - Infeld, Leopold, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Kemble, Edwin C., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Klein, Oskar, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Kronig, Ralph, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Kuhn, H. G., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Kuhn, Werner, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Kurti, Nicholas, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Landau, L. D., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Landé, Alfred, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Langevin, Jean, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Laporte, Otto, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Lindsay, Robert Bruce, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Mayer, Maria Goeppert, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Meissner, Walther, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Meitner, Lise, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Minkowski, Rudolf, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous Leads to Manuscripts, 1961-1964; 3.0 Item(s) 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Møller, Christian, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Mott, Nevill Francis, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Mulliken, Robert Sanderson, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Nordheim, Lothar, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Pauli, Wolfgang, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Peierls, Rudolf Ernst, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Perrin, Francis, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Pohl, Robert Wichard, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Polanyi, Michael, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Rabi, I. I., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Rasetti, Franco and Enrico Persico, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Reiche, Fritz, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Rosenfeld, Leon, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Rosseland, Svein, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Rubinowicz, Adalbert, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Rutherford, Ernest, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Schrödinger, Frau Erwin, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Schultz, Betty, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Segrè, Emilio, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Slater, John C., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Stern, Otto, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Thirring, Hans, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Thomas, Llewellyn H., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Thomson, George Paget, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Uhlenbeck, George Eugene, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Ullmo, Jean, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Urey, Harold Clayton, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Van Vleck, J. H., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Volmer, Max, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Von Hippel, Arthur R., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Von Karman, Theodore, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Waller, Ivar, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Wentzel, Gregor, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Wheeler, John Archibald, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Wiener, Norbert, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Wigner, Eugene Paul, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
  - Yukawa, Hideki, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 21)
- IX. Working Papers - Miscellaneous, 4.0 Linear feet (Box 22)
  - French Science, 9.0 p.; Paul, C. B. (Box 22)
    Essay entitled "Influences on French Theoretical Physics, 1900-1925."
  - Historique des Instituts internationaux de Physique et de Chimie Solvay depuis leur fondation jusqu'à la deuxième guerre Mondiale, 107.0 p.; Pelseneer, Jean, 1903-1985 (Box 22)
  - Lists of Sources
    - List of Interviews - Work Sheets, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Preliminary List: Dead Significant Physicists, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Preliminary List: Sources in the U. S. A., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Preliminary List: Sources outside U. S. A., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Preliminary Lists of Sources - Work Sheets, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
  - Notes on Methods, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Notes: Duplication of Manucripts, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Notes on Interviewing Methods, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Notes on Research Methods, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Notes on Schematic Biographies Procedures, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
  - Collective Mailing
    - Announcement to Scientific Journals, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Letter to Joint Committee, 16 October 1961; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Replies to Priority List, 1961; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Description of Project, November 1961; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Checklist, February 1962; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Requests for Cooperation, 15 February 1962; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Progress Report, 26 April 1962; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
    - First Year-End Report, 8 August 1962; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
    - Letter to Joint Committee, 7 December 1962; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
    - Memorandum to Joint Committee, 4 February 1963; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
    - Letter to George E. Uhlenbeck. (Copies to Members of Joint Committee), 18 October 1963; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
    - Second Year-End Report, 28 October 1963; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
  - Deutsche Bücherei Leipzig, Deutsche Nationalbibliothek..., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
  - Library Survey
    - Archive for the History of Quantum Physics
      - Correspondence, 1962; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
      - Correspondence, 1964; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
      - Correspondence, 1966; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1969; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
      - Correspondence, 1973; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
      - Interview Data, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
      - Joint Committee, Minutes, 1960-1964, 1966-1968; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
      - Proposal to N.S.F., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
      - Sources for History of Quantum Physics - Typed Draft, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 23)
    - [Interview with Louis de Broglie], 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous Archival Materials, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Summary Library Survey, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Address Lists, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - [Library Letter], 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Library Letter (Extra Copies), 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Holton's Bibliography, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Library Lists, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Academy Check Lists, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Preliminary Replies to Library Letter, 1963; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Fritz London, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Library Project Correspondence, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Work Sheets for Academy Survey, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Replies: Letters to Academies, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Negative Replies to Library Survey Letter, 1963; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Positive Replies to Library Survey Letter, 1963; 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
    - Random Leads, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 24)
  - Sources for the History of Quantum Physics, 1.0 Linear feet (Box 25)
    - General and Regional Information, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
    - Physicists (Deceased), 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
    - Living European Physicists, 10.0 Item(s) 10 folders (Box 25)
      - A - B, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - C - D, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - E - F - G, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - H - I - J, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - K - L, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - M - N, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - O - P - Q, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - R - S, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - T - U - V, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - W - X - Y - Z, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
    - Regional Lists, 11.0 Item(s) 11 folders (Box 25)
      - Austria and Switzerland, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - Belgium and the Netherlands, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - Berlin, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - Eastern Germany and Poland, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - France, Italy, and Spain, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - Great Britain and Ireland, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - Northern Germany, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - Scandinavia, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - Southern Germany, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - Pre-War Germany, 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)
      - U.S.S.R., 1.0 Item(s) 1 folder (Box 25)